findmyperfectrates.com 2011-05-19

# FindMyPerfectRates | Insurance Problem Solved

## FindMyPerfectRates.com Privacy Policy Statement

_This privacy policy was last updated on March 15th, 2011_

FindMyPerfectRates is owned by QuoteWizard.com LLC. FindMyPerfectRates is committed to protecting your private information. This Privacy Statement describes the information that we collect when you visit one of our sites. It also describes how we use that information, and how you can update it. We reserve the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Statement at any time. Please re-visit this page occasionally to check for updates. 

## Information We Collect

Collecting various types of information from our visitors allows FindMyPerfectRates to periodically adjust our site to meet our users' needs and expectations. Some of this information is collected automatically, through cookies. Other information is collected when you register for any of our online services, or when you request information from one of our insurance partners. 

## Information Collected Automatically

Some information is automatically sent to FindMyPerfectRates by your browser or Internet session each time you visit one of our sites. These types of information include: 

  * The name of your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator.
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, Earthlink, etc.
  * You computer's operating system, e.g., Windows, Macintosh, UNIX, Linux. 
  * Your navigation path, e.g., the URL(s) that you use to access our site, which of our pages you visit, and where you go when you leave. 
  * Your IP address. 

This information allows us to see how users are finding our sites, and which pages are visited the most often. We can then use this information to make our web sites more useful and more user-friendly. 

## Information You Provide to Us

In addition to the information automatically collected by your browser, FindMyPerfectRates also collects information that you provide to us when you request quote information. 

Our web sites provide users with the opportunity to request quote information from insurance providers and brokers. To do this, we collect contact information (name, address, phone number, email address, gender, age, work experience, etc.) as well as information relevant to the applicant's insurability (driver history, vehicle usage, etc). This contact information is then provided to the insurance partners from which the user has requested quote information. 

FindMyPerfectRates uses cookies to store contact information for each user. If the user uses our site to make further requests for quote information, their contact information will automatically be used to pre-populate contact forms. FindMyPerfectRates also collects customer interest information (e.g. Requests for E-Mail Newsletters) to determine what information the customer wishes to be sent after using our service. 

By submitting a quote request, you authorize FindMyPerfectRates to provide your information to insurance agents, both local and national. You also authorize FindMyPerfectRates to provide your information to one of our third party agent networks in the event that our primary agent network has few or no agents in your zip code. You authorize these agent networks to share your information with their vendors, suppliers, and insurance carriers in order to generate information for your quotes. By submitting a quote request, you acknowledge that FindMyPerfectRates’s service requires you to agree that our partner companies may obtain a consumer report or credit score from a consumer reporting agency (also known as a credit bureau) and that these partner companies do not have the right to obtain a consumer report or credit score without your written instruction which you are granting by clicking the submit button. Accordingly, by submitting a quote request you instruct consumer reporting agencies to provide a consumer report or credit score on you to these partner companies if requested within a reasonable date from the time you submit information to FindMyPerfectRates. In the event that one of our partner companies obtains this credit information that partner company will not share this information with any other party, including insurance carriers, but insurance carriers may elect to obtain credit information on their own in connection with the quoting and underwriting of the requested insurance. Where permitted by law, some insurance companies or their agents may confirm your information, through the use of consumer reports, which may include credit score and driving record. 

If you provide a cell phone number with your contact information, FindMyPerfectRates and/or FindMyPerfectRates's clients may dial this number, including autodialing of this number, to provide quote information and/or seek additional information in order to provide a quote. 

## How We Use This Information

The information that is automatically collected by our web site allows FindMyPerfectRates to further develop and improve the layout, design, and usability of the site, in order to better serve your Internet needs. Information you provide to us is used for marketing purposes, and may result in follow-up communications. 

FindMyPerfectRates may share personally identifiable information with third-party businesses for the purpose of direct marketing, specifically e-mail marketing. All third parties are bound by the CAN SPAM Act (s.877) of 2003, and are required to be in full compliance of all consumer opt-out rules and regulations. 

## How Our Insurance Partners May Use This Information

IMPORTANT: All proposed named insured listed on this application must be made aware of the following: 

In order to provide you with the most accurate quotes possible, insurance companies may need to obtain additional background information about you. As an example Consumer reports may be ordered in connection with your insurance application. These reports provide information that may assist in determining your eligibility for insurance and the price you may be charged. Consumer reports may also be used for updates, renewals or extensions of this insurance. The insurance company may also obtain and use a credit-based insurance score based on information contained in your credit report. The insurance company may use a third party in connection with the development of the insurance score. 

## Your Rights—Our Obligations 

The company respects the privacy of users visiting our sites and will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of personal information. On occasion, we may use certain directory information that we collect from you to send you information about products and services, or updates and other information that we think may be of interest to you. We may share this information with our insurance partners to bring similar information to your attention. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. Please contact us to request that your name and address should be removed from our lists. If you do not want to receive our e-mail marketing, please submit a request to have your e-mail address removed by e-mailing: unsubscribe@FindMyPerfectRates.com. 

Other than directory information, the data that you provide to us as you use the web site will be held in strict confidence by the company, and will be used for company purposes only. 

## Our Security Measures

Our web sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of the information under our control. 

## Why We Use "Cookies" 

When you visit some of our sites, we use cookies to keep track of your information. A "cookie" is a small piece of program code that resides on your computer and stores your contact information for all of our "Request Information" sites. Each time you visit our site, the cookie uses the stored information to pre-populate our online forms, so that you do not have to re-enter your contact information as you move from one site to another. 

## Links From Our Site To Other Sites

Some of our sites may contain links to other sites external to our sites. When you access these external web sites, the providers of the sites will have access to certain information about you. FindMyPerfectRates is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any web sites which we do not directly control. 

## Definitions

## Cookies

Data created by a web server that is stored on a user's computer. A cookie provides a way for the web site to keep track of a user's patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user's own hard disk. 

The cookies contain a range of URLs (web addresses) for which they are valid. When the browser encounters those URLs again, it sends those specific cookies to the Web server. For example, if a user's ID is stored as a cookie, it saves that person from typing in the same information all over again when accessing that service for the second and subsequent time during the same browser session. 

You can opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu. 

## IP (Internet Protocol) Address

This is the address of a computer attached to a TCP/IP network. Every client and server station must have a unique IP address. Client workstations have either a permanent address or one that is dynamically assigned for each dial-up session. IP addresses are written as four sets of numbers separated by periods; for example, 204.171.64.2. 

## Browser Session

A browser session is defined as the period of time a browser is in consecutive use. The session begins when you open the browser and ends when you close it. When you re-open the browser, you begin a new session. 

## SSL Encryption (Secure Sockets Layer)

The leading security protocol on the Internet. When an SSL session is started, the browser sends its public key to the server so that the server can securely send a secret key to the browser. The browser and server exchange data via secret key encryption during that session. FindMyPerfectRates also uses SSL encryption whenever we display your personal information (e.g., name and address, scheduled courses, grades). 

## URL (Uniform Resource Locator)

An Internet address. URLs are used to locate sites on the Internet and to navigate between sites and pages within sites. The URL for FindMyPerfectRates is www.FindMyPerfectRates.com.
